NORA ATHIRA YASMIN KASSIM

Shah Alam, Selangor, Malaysia



athira.ysmn@gmail.com



+60192549717



linkedin.com/in/noraathira



https://n-athrysmn.github.io/first-portfolio/

Summary

Motivated Junior Software Engineer with Bachelor Degree of Computer Science in Software Engineering. Experience researching, designing and implementing new features as part of larger development team. Experience includes writing documentation, preparing release packages and writing test cases.

Created complete prototype using Figma, then translated the design using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Experienced in JavaScript libraries, frameworks and runtime environment like ReactJS, jQuery, NodeJS, Angular, and Chartis. Also experienced in other frameworks like Bootstrap, Laravel and Tailwindcss.

Experience



Full Stack Engineer

ArRiyad Resources

Dec 2022 - Present (3 months)

- Collaborated with team to analyze system solutions based on client requirements.
- · Discussed project progress with customers, collected feedback on different stages and directly addressed concerns.
- Developed support patches for existing software.
- Planned and developed interfaces that simplified overall management and offered ease of use.

Document Controller

Padu Rok Resources SDN BHD

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022 (4 months)

- Proofread filenames, titles and submittal details to streamline submittal and avoid rejection.
- · Carefully reviewed all documents and reports for completeness and accuracy.
- · Enforced use of standardized forms and templates to achieve uniformity of communications across departments and functions.
- · Maintained document archive and file server of approved documents and drawings to provide easy traceability and retrievability.

Application Engineer

LCP Buildsoft Technology (M) Sdn Bhd

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022 (7 months)

- Exhibited strong technical aptitude and application expertise resulting in optimized performance, continuous improvement recommendations and product innovation.
- Partnered with development team on product development and application support plans.
- Communicated technical development stages and provided design support to stakeholders.
- Supported software integration and implemented maintenance enhancements.

UI/UX Designer

GR TECH SDN BHD

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022 (6 months)

- · Adapted quickly to constantly changing, deadline-driven environment.
- Used content creation tools like Figma and digital media to design web sites.
- Prioritized and problem-solved several tasks concurrently with minimum supervision.
- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5, and CSS3.

6 Frontend Web Developer

Top Click E-Services Sdn Bhd

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

- Adapted quickly to constantly changing, deadline-driven environment.
- Shadowed developers to learn key details about job duties and tasks.
- Studied user requirements to gain strong understanding of project initiatives and deadlines.
- Boosted web traffic by improving navigation and rectifying bottlenecks.

Education

座 Universiti Malaysia Terengganu

Bachelor in computer science, Computer Software Engineering 2018 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications

G Google Cloud Certified in G Suite - Google

Issued Oct 2020 - Expires Oct 2022 8cSE9s

Skills

Figma (Software) • Laravel • Node.js • WordPress • Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • JavaServer Pages (JSP) • C++ • Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) • React.js